Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part I WAG.025.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Administrative and Organizational Records
  - Subseries I:F: Scrapbooks, 1936-1947 [Note: These scrapbooks were in extremely fragile condition and were destroyed after filming.]
    - Clippings, May 1945-Dec 1945
      Reel#: 53
    - Clippings, Jan 1946
    - Clippings, Jan 1946-Apr 1946
    - Clippings, Apr 1946-May 1946
      Reel#: 54
    - Clippings, Jun 1946-Dec 1946
    - Clippings, Aug 1946-Dec 1946
    - Clippings, Jan 1947-Feb 1947
    - Clippings, Jan 1947-May 1947
    - Clippings, Jun 1947-Aug 1947
      Reel#: 55
    - Clippings, Sep 1947-Dec 1947
- Series II: American Cities (arranged alphabetically by state and within each state by city)
  - American Cities: General, 1937, 1944-1946 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Reel#: 56
  - Alabama: General, 1945, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Birmingham, AL, 1941-1947 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Arkansas: General, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - California: General, 1943-1947 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Fresno, CA, 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles, CA, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles, CA, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles, CA, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Oct 1940-Dec 1940 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1941-Apr 1941 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Los Angeles, CA, May 1941-Aug 1941 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Sep 1941-Oct 1941 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Reel#: 57
  - Los Angeles, CA, Nov 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1942-Mar 1942 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Apr 1942-Jun 1942 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jul 1942-Sep 1942 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Oct 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1943-Jun 1943 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jul 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1944-Jun 1944 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jul 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    Reel#: 58
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1945-Jun 1945 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jul 1945-Sep 1945 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Oct 1945-Dec 1945 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1946-Mar 1946 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Apr 1946-Jun 1946 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jul 1946-Sep 1946 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Oct 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Reel#: 59
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1947-Mar 1947 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Apr 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jul 1947-Sep 1947 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Oct 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Oakland, CA, 1937, 1941-1947 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Petaluma, CA, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - San Diego, CA, 1941-1945, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - San Francisco, CA, 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - San Francisco, CA, 1943-1947 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    Reel#: 60
  - San Jose, CA, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Stockton, CA, 1942-1944 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Colorado: General, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Denver, CO, 1941-1947 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut: General, 1941-1947 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Ansonia, CT, 1941-1947 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Bridgeport, CT, 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Bridgeport, CT, 1943-1947 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Bristol, CT, 1941-1943 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Hartford, CT, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Hartford, CT, 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Hartford, CT, 1943-1947 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - New Britain, CT, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - New Haven, CT, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - New Haven, CT, 1941-1945, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - New London, CT, 1941-1946 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Norwich, CT, 1941-1943 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Norwich, CT, 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - South Norwalk, CT, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    Reel#: 61
  - Waterbury, CT, 1941-1947 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Willimantic, CT, 1943-1947 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Wilmington, DE, 1941-1947 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Florida: General, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Jacksonville, FL, 1935-1937 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Jacksonville, FL, 1941-1944, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Miami, FL, 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Miami, FL, 1941-1945 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Miami, FL, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - West Palm Beach, FL, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Georgia: General, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Albany, GA, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Atlanta, GA, 1937, 1941-1942 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Atlanta, GA, 1943-1945 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Atlanta, GA, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Savannah, GA, 1941-1943 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Savannah, GA, 1944-1947 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Illinois: General, 1942, 1944, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Aurora, IL, 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Champaign, IL, 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Chicago, IL, 1934-1937 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Chicago, IL, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    Reel#: 62
  - Chicago, IL, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Chicago, IL, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1941-Apr 1941 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Chicago, IL, May 1941-Aug 1941 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Chicago, IL, Sep 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1942-Apr 1942 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Chicago, IL, May 1942-Aug 1942 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Chicago, IL, Sep 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1943-Jun 1943 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    Reel#: 63
  - Chicago, IL, Jul 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1944-Jun 1944 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Chicago, IL, Jul 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1945-Jul 1945 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Chicago, IL, Aug 1945-Dec 1945 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1946-Mar 1946 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Chicago, IL, Apr 1946-Jun 1946 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Chicago, IL, Jul 1946-Aug 1946 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Reel#: 64
  - Chicago, IL, Sep 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1947-Apr 1947 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Chicago, IL, May 1947-Aug 1947 (Box 24, Folder 7A)
  - Chicago, IL, Sep 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Indiana: General, 1943, 1945-1946 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Reel#: 65
  - Anderson, IN, 1945-1946 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Fort Wayne, IN, 1945-1946 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Hammond, IN, 1944, 1946-1947 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Indianapolis, IN, 1943-1947 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - South Bend, IN, 1942-1947 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Terre Haute, IN, 1945-1946 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Valparaiso, IN, 1945-1946 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Iowa: General, 1943-1947 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Des Moines, IA, 1941-1947 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Sioux City, IA, 1941-1947 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Kansas: General, 1946-1947 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Kentucky: General, 1946-1947 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - New Orleans, LA, 1941-1947 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Shreveport, LA, 1937, 1941-1947 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Maine: General, 1942-1944 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1934-1935, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1940-1941 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Bethesda, MD, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Massachusetts: General, 1940-1947 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Reel#: 66
  - Boston, MA, 1934-1937 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Boston, MA, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Boston, MA, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Boston, MA, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Boston, MA, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Boston, MA, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Boston, MA, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Boston, MA, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Boston, MA, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Brockton, MA, 1943-1945 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Chelsea, MA, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Dorchester, MA, 1945, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Fall River, MA, 1942-1947 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Holyoke, MA, 1943-1946 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Lawrence, MA, 1941-1943 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Lawrence, MA, 1944-1947 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    Reel#: 67
  - Lowell, MA, 1943-1946 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Lynn, MA, 1942-1946 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - New Bedford, MA, 1941-1945 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Peabody, MA, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Springfield, MA, 1937-1938, 1941-1947 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Worcester, MA, 1941-1947 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Michigan: General, 1944-1947 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Ann Arbor,MI, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Battle Creek, MI, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Bay City, MI, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Benton Harbor, MI, 1945-1947 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Detroit, MI, 1935-1938 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Detroit, MI, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Detroit, MI, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Detroit, MI, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Detroit, MI, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Detroit, MI, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Detroit, MI, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    Reel#: 68
  - Detroit, MI, Jan 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Detroit, MI, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Flint, MI, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Grand Rapids, MI, 1942-1947 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Lansing, MI, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Mount Clemens, MI, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Muskegon, MI, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Pontiac, MI, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Saginaw, MI, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Minnesota: General, 1944, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Duluth, MN, 1941-1946 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Minneapolis, MN, 1937-1947 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Missouri: General, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Cape Girardeau, MO, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Jefferson City, MO, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Joplin, MO, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Kansas City, MO, 1941, 1943-1947 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - St. Joseph, MO, 1941-1943, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - St. Louis, MO, 1937, 1941-1947 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Sedalia, MO, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    Reel#: 69
  - Montana: General, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Billings, MT, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Lincoln, NE, 1941-1942, 1944-1947 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Omaha, NE, 1941-1947 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - New Hampshire: General, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - New Jersey: General, 1935-1937 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - New Jersey: General, 1941-1946 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - New Jersey: General, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Asbury Park, NJ, 1942-1944, 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Atlantic City, NJ, 1942-1944, 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Elizabeth, NJ, 1936, 1941-1947 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Hackensack, NJ, 1942-1945 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Highland Park, NJ, 1942-1944, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Hightstown, NJ, 1942-1947 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Hoboken, NJ, 1942-1944, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Jersey City, NJ, 1941-1947 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Lakewood, NJ, 1935-1936, 1941-1947 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Long Branch, NJ, 1943-1947 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Morristown, NJ, 1941-1947 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - New Brunswick, NJ, 1942-1945, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Newark, NJ, 1934-1938 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Newark, NJ, 1941-1943 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Newark, NJ, 1944-1947 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    Reel#: 70
  - Passaic, NJ, 1941-1946 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Passaic, NJ, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Paterson, NJ, 1934-1938 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Paterson, NJ, 1941-1943 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Paterson, NJ, 1944-1947 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Perth Amboy, NJ, 1938, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Plainfield, NJ, 1942-1943 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Roosevelt, NJ, 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Roselle, NJ, 1937, 1941-1947 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Trenton, NJ, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Union City, NJ, 1942-1943, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - West New York, NJ, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - New York: General, 1941-1947 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Albany, NY, 1937, 1941, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Bronx, NY, 1941-1945 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    Reel#: 71
  - Bronx, NY, 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Brooklyn, NY, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1935-1937 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - College Point, NY, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Ellenville, NY, 1941-1945 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Ferndale, NY, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Gloversville, NY, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Kingston, NY, 1943-1945 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Liberty, NY, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Monticello, NY, 1937, 1941-1946 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - New Rochelle, NY, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Newburgh, NY, 1942-1943, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Portchester, NY, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Rochester, NY, 1937, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Rochester, NY, 1944-1947 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Schenectady, NY, 1937, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - South Fallsburg, NY, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Spring Valley, NY, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Syracuse, NY, 1937, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Syracuse, NY, 1944-1947 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    Reel#: 72
  - Utica, NY, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Woodridge, NY, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - North Carolina: General, 1944, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Ohio: General, 1945-1946 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Akron, OH, 1942-1947 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Cincinnati, OH, 1941-1947 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1935-1938 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1940-1941 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    Reel#: 73
  - Columbus, OH, 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Dayton, OH, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Lorain, OH, 1941, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Springfield, OH, 1945-1946 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Toledo, OH, 1941-1947 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Youngstown, OH, 1943-1944, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Portland, OR, 1941, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Pennsylvania: General, 1945-1947 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Allentown, PA, 1942, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - East Stroudsburg, PA, 1941, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Erie, PA, 1941-1944 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Harrisburg, PA, 1941-1943, 1945-1946 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Kingston, PA, 1941-1942, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Monessen, PA, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - New Kensington, PA, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1934-1937 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1940-1942 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Reel#: 74
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1934-1937 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1940-1942 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Reading, PA, 1941-1942, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Scranton, PA, 1941-1946 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Shamokin, PA, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Wilkes-Barre, PA, 1941-1947 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Providence, RI, 1941-1946 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - South Carolina: General, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Tennessee: General, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Chattanooga, TN, 1941-1947 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Memphis, TN, 1941-1943, 1945-1947 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Nashville, TN, 1941-1943, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Texas: General, 1943, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    Reel#: 75
  - Dallas, TX, 1941-1945 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Galveston, TX, 1941-1943 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Galveston, TX, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Galveston, TX, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Houston, TX, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Houston, TX, 1941-1943 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Houston, TX, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Houston, TX, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - San Antonio, TX, 1941-1943, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Waco, TX, 1941-1946 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Virginia: General, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Norfolk, VA, 1941, 1943, 1945-1947 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Richmond, VA, 1940-1947 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Washington: General, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Seattle, WA, 1937, 1941-1947 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Tacoma, WA, 1942, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Washington, DC, 1934-1938 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Washington, DC, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Washington, DC, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Washington, DC, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    Reel#: 76
  - Washington, DC, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - West Virginia: General, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Wisconsin: General, 1941-1945 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Beloit, WI, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Fond du Lac, WI, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Green Bay, WI, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Madison, WI, 1935, 1942- (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Manitowoc, WI, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Milwaukee, WI, 1941-1943, 1945-1947 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Oshkosh, WI, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Racine, WI Series III: Foreign Countries (arranged alphabetically by country), 1943, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 50)
- Series III: Foreign Countries (arranged alphabetically by country)
  - Africa: General, 1944-1947 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Reel#: 77
  - Algeria, 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Argentina, 1944-1946 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Argentina, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Australia, 1941-1943 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Australia, 1944-1946 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Australia, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Austria, undated, 1943-1947 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Belgium, 1940-1944 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Belgium, Jan 1945-Aug 1945 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Belgium, Sep 1945-Dec 1945 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Reel#: 78
  - Belgium, Jan 1946-Jun 1946 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Belgium, Jul 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Belgium, Jan 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Belgium, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Brazil, 1939, 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Bulgaria, 1943, 1945-1947 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Canada: General, 1935-1939 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Canada: General, 1941-1947 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Canada: Visas, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    Reel#: 79
  - Canada: Montreal, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1941-Jun 1941 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jul 1941-Sep 1941 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Canada: Montreal, Oct 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Canada: Montreal, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Canada: Montreal, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1944-Jul 1944 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Reel#: 80
  - Canada: Montreal, Aug 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1945-Jul 1945 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Canada: Montreal, Aug 1945-Dec 1945 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1946-May 1946 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jun 1946-Sep 1946 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Canada: Montreal, Oct 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1947-Feb 1947 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Canada: Montreal, Mar 1947-Apr 1947 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Reel#: 81
  - Canada: Montreal, May 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jul 1947-Aug 1947 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Canada: Montreal, Sep 1947-Oct 1947 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Canada: Montreal, Nov 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Canada: Ottawa, 1941-1947 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1937-1938 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    Reel#: 82
  - Canada: Toronto, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Canada: Toronto, Jan 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Canada: Toronto, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Canada: Vancouver, 1941-1942, 1944-1946 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Canada: Windsor, 1941-1947 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Reel#: 83
  - Canada: Winnipeg, 1937 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Canada: Winnipeg, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Canada: Winnipeg, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Canada: Winnipeg, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Canada: Winnipeg, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Canada: Winnipeg, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Canada: Winnipeg, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Chile, 1942, 1946-1947 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - China, Jan 1938-Oct 1938 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - China, Nov 1938-Dec 1938 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - China, 1939-1940 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - China, 1941-1944 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - China, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    Reel#: 84
  - China, Jan 1946-Apr 1946 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - China, May 1946-Aug 1946 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - China, Sep 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - China, Jan 1947-Apr 1947 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - China, May 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Cuba, 1939-1941 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Cuba, 1942-1944 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Cuba, 1945-1947 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    Reel#: 85
  - Cyprus, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1938, 1941-1943 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1944-1947 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Denmark, 1943-1944, 1946-1947 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Ecuador, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Egypt, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - England, 1939-1941 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - England, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - England, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - England, Jan 1944-Apr 1944 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - England, May 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Reel#: 86
  - England, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - England, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - England, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Finland, 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - France, 1937-1939 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - France, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - France, Jan 1941-May 1941 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - France, Jun 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - France, Jan 1942-Mar 1942 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Reel#: 87
  - France, Apr 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - France, Jan 1943-May 1943 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - France, Jun 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - France, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - France, Jan 1945-Mar 1945 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - France, Apr 1945-Sep 1945 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - France, Oct 1945-Dec 1945 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - France, Jan 1946 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - France, Feb 1946-Mar 1946 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    Reel#: 88
  - France, Apr 1946-May 1946 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - France, Jun 1946-Sep 1946 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - France, Oct 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - France, Jan 1947-Mar 1947 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - France, Apr 1947-May 1947 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - France, Jun 1947-Jul 1947 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    Reel#: 89
  - France, Aug-47-Sep 1947 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - France, Oct 1947 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - France, Nov 1947 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - France, Dec 1947 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Germany, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Germany, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Germany, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Germany, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Reel#: 90
  - Germany, Jan 1947-Feb 1947 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Germany, Mar 1947-May 1947 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Germany, Jun 1947-Jul 1947 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Germany, Aug 1947 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Germany, Sep 1947-Oct 1947 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Germany, Nov 1947 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Germany, Dec 1947 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    Reel#: 91
  - Greece, 1942-1946 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Hungary, 1942-1945 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Hungary, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - India, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Iran, 1942-1943 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Italy, 1943-1945 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Italy, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Italy, Jan 1947-Jul 1947 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Italy, Aug 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Japan, Oct 1940-May 1941 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    Reel#: 92